Entertainment... district?
You know, that place with all the beautiful... the shapely...
You get what I'm trying to say, right? Come on!
Listen up!
I am a god!
You three are trash!
That's the first bit of info you need to pound into your heads!
So drag it in!
You turn into dogs if I say so!
Turn into monkeys if I tell you!
So be ready to bend over backwards, pander to my every whim, and worship me endlessly!
And remember above all else, I am a god!
Oh, this guy is crazy.
Quick question, Mr. Uzui. What exactly are you the god of?
Please tell me he's playing dumb.
Good question, pupil! You have great potential!
What potential lies in a stupid question like that?
I am the god of festivals. The god of flashiness.
Yeah, there's no doubt about it. He's the god of stupidity and idiots.
Well, I am the king of the mountains! It's a pleasure to meet you, god of festivals!
The wolf?
I've never heard of you. That's odd.
Something about you creeps me out.
You're kidding right?!
You two are a match made in heaven! Princeworthy!
You are creepy! I'll show you to me how he knows that!
Super creepy.
He's totally oblivious to the fact that they're basically the same person, isn't he?
Right, that's enough fooling around. Let's go.
Follow me.
He disappeared? Look!
He's fast! Look how far he got! He's the size of a sesame seed!
So this is the power of the god of festivals?
No way. He's just Mr. Uzui Tengya and a Hashira.
What are you waiting around for? We have to go after him!
Please be careful! Please be careful!
Keep Travels!
Karli
Okay.
Keep Travels!
Take pocket at
Please be careful!
Check my驚き
Love is false Europe is false.
Someone who makes love you!
Thank you all!
Chained
Thank you
Ya, ya, ya, ya...
Oh-oh!
Ah!
Listen, you three. Try not to stand out. We're only here to case the joint. And whatever you do, don't get out of the carriage.
Stop it! What do you think you're doing? Where are you going?
Come back, you two!
What a bunch of hard-headed idiots!
Settle down, Inosuke.
Get back here, damn it! I'm talking to you, too! Are you listening to me?
It's so bright. It looks like it's daytime.
Allow me to introduce you to the Yoshiwara Entertainment District, awash in vanity and desire.
Flashy, isn't it?
What kind of place is this? There's too many people to even count!
Big way, Chucks! To now coming through!
Get back here, moron!
Hey! Where'd the annoying kid with the yellow hair go?
What?
Well, aren't you a handsome one?
Why don't you come and join us?
If you're hungry, we have candy!
No need to be shy, young man.
Beautiful ladies who make the first move? What am I gonna do?
Not so fast! You're too young for that kind of stuff.
Take notes, you three. During the day, this place is quiet as a ghost town. But at night, it roars to life with all kinds of people. Ideal circumstances for a demon.
The women here are also unique. Many become courtesans and are sold off to pay their debts.
In return, they're given food, clothing and lodging. And if they climb up the ranks, a rich man might buy out their contracts.
The highest-ranking courtesan is referred to as Oiran, and she's on a whole different level.
Her beauty and intelligence are unrivaled, and she's mastered every traditional art.
A woman of distinction, bathed in her house's resources, to become their shining star.
She sounds incredible.
I think that's enough reconnaissance for now. Let's go.
Sorry to impose.
Listen up, you three.
Once you're in the entertainment district, you should try to seek out my wives.
I'll search for any info on the demons.
This is completely ridiculous!
Huh?
You're joking, right?
How dare you order us to waste our time finding a bride for you, huh?
What? Why did I ever ask for something like that?
Shut up! I'm not done talking here!
I need to, please!
Just because a freak like you has no luck with the ladies doesn't make it okay to use demon slayers like us for such a pitiful reason!
We're not helping you find a wife, you creep!
What are you babbling about, idiot?
I'm talking about my wives who've infiltrated the entertainment district and are hard at work gathering intel!
Well, I've stopped receiving regular check-ins, so I need to ensure they're still safe!
I suppose that is what a guy like you would fantasize.
You damn punk!
Here's your proof. Letters that were sent to me by Kasugai Krohn.
There's quite a lot of them here. She must have been undercover for quite some time.
Oh, well, I do have three wives.
What? Did you say wives? In three?
Three? Three? Three? Three wives? There's no way!
How did you of all people manage to get three wives?
This is some kind of sick show!
You got a problem with that, kid?
Um, excuse me, but I noticed that in the letters they sent you, they all seem to keep reminding you not to stand out when you come.
Which is why I'm sending you three!
So what are we going to do, exactly?
Disguise yourselves, of course, and as much as I hate it, in an unflashy way.
All three of my wives are brilliant ninjas known as kunoichis.
I was almost certain that this district would be the perfect place for the demons, but when I went in as a customer, I couldn't get any info on them.
So I sent each of them in to get closer than a customer ever could.
Since I've already narrowed down the likeliest houses to three, you all will search for my wives there and try to gather information.
Suma of the Tokito house, Makio of the Ogimoto house, and Hinatsuru of the Kyogoku house.
They're probably all dead if they stopped writing.
Pardon my intrusion, sir, but I brought back all of the items you requested earlier.
Thank you.
Oh my goodness.
These three girls are certainly a homely bunch, aren't they?
Oh, sorry. I'm afraid we're not looking to hire it this time.
I beg of you to find it in your heart to reconsider.
I believe that under your training, madam, their beauty will bloom in no time.
That's very flattering, but...
Well, I suppose taking in one wouldn't be a problem.
I can assure you that you won't be disappointed.
You may pick whichever girl you'd like.
If we can choose, then I think we'll take the one in the middle.
She looks the most obedient.
I promise to work as hard as I can.
Great. Now I'm stuck with you two brats.
I'm gonna have to pay someone to take you.
Stop talking to me. I don't want to hear it from you.
Are you upset you have to dress up as a girl?
You said you'd do anything I asked, right?
I don't give a damn that I'm dressed up like a girl, you moron.
It's that face of yours.
You think you're such hot stuff?
It pisses me the hell off!
Hey, look! Seems like there's a whole bunch of people swarming around over there.
Oh, that there is house Tokito's Oiran.
Her name is Koinatsu.
The highest-ranking courtesan is going off to meet her suitor.
How's that for being flashy?
That her?!
Are you telling me that's your wife?!
How did you get with a knockout like her?!
And what, you have three of them?!
Do they all look like that, huh? Do they?!
She's not my wife!
Why did she walk so slow?
She'd be killed instantly if we were in the mountains.
Excuse me, sir, but I'll be taking this girl back to my house now, if that's all right.
I see. And you must be...
Forgive me. I am the chaperone of the Ogimoto house.
Well, if she managed to catch the eye of the Ogimoto house, how could I refuse?
May I ask what it was about her that caught your attention?
Yes. Her beauty is unlike any I have ever seen.
Take care of yourself out there, Inoko!
Oh, no! I'm the only one left here!
Take a look at her now!
She's perfect!
I wasn't sure with all that makeup plastered over her face, but my goodness!
I can't believe I was able to buy this unrefined beauty for such a low price!
Mmm.
I'm gonna train this woman like nobody's business!
When I'm through, she'll be in more demand than Kyokoku house's Warabihime or Tokito house's Koinatsu!
This girl certainly has some heft to her, though, doesn't she?
Well, it's better for a girl to be plump and curvy than scurvy, right?
It certainly seems like she's more muscular than Plump.
Ah...
Wow! That girl sure can't play the shamisen!
No kidding! So dynamic! Do you know anything about her?
I know she has a good ear for music. I was told she could play the shamisen or Koto after just one listen.
It's a pity about her looks, though. I'm surprised she got taken in here. She may be hideous, but I heard the man who brought her here was drop-dead gorgeous!
Oh! Was he really? I wish I could have seen him! The chaperone lady was totally smitten!
I've never been more certain. That girl will rise to the top.
What?
Her shamisen is speaking for her. She intends to get back at the man who abandoned her. That girl has serious backbone.
I... I see.
If you take her, you can have her clean the toilets or do whatever you want, really. Hell, you don't even have to pay! Just take her!
I'm gonna make that jerk pay for this! Just watch me become the number one oiron in Yoshiwara!
Sumiko, do you have a minute?
Sure.
Sorry to bother you, but we're short-staffed. Could you help carry these up the stairs?
It'd be my pleasure. I'll take care of it, no problem.
Thank you, Sumiko. Nice to have a hard worker around.
I apologize for removing your makeup yesterday. I feel like it's partially our fault the house madam found that scar of yours.
Relax, my dear! There's no use lashing out at this poor child!
I'm fine. Just thankful that they're letting me work here.
My, my! That new girl is rather burly!
Burly, indeed.
They say the Kyogoku House's madam died from falling out of a window.
That's awful! Let's be careful, okay?
And have you noticed some of the older girls running away committing ashinuke?
That's scary!
What even is ashinuke?
That's a lot of baggage to carry.
There we go.
I think they're all gifts for oiron koinatsu.
You said you've never heard of ashinuke?
It's probably a good thing you haven't.
Ashinuke means to run away without paying off your debts.
And it's really bad if you get caught.
Why do they do that?
Some people try running away in order to be with the man they're in love with.
Right, like oiron suma did the other day.
Suma? That's Mr. Uzui's wife.
Listen.
You two shouldn't be spreading rumors.
After all, nobody knows her whereabouts now.
Who knows what happened to her?
Fine.
You brought these up for yourself.
Thank you.
Oh, it's my pleasure.
Come here.
Take this candy as my thanks.
Keep it secret or you'll have to share it.
Hey, I want some candy.
Me too! Me too!
Now, now. I gave you some earlier.
Um...
Did oiron suma really commit ashinuke?
May I ask why you're so curious about that?
She has her guard up.
But I've got to find a way around it and ask about Miss Suma.
It's just...
Candy, please!
Oiron suma is...
She's actually...
Believe it or not...
She's my...
Elder sister!
What?
I think I understand now.
So you were sold shortly after your sister.
Yes, that's right.
The entire time she was here with you, I was exchanging letters with her.
I promise you she isn't the type of person who would commit ashinuke.
Oh, I had no idea.
I was surprised as well.
I could hardly believe that Suma would commit ashinuke.
She was such a well-behaved girl.
There were no signs that she was infatuated with any man.
But they ended up finding her diary.
I heard they read through the entire thing and found she'd written about running off.
Ashinuke...
Demons couldn't ask for a more perfect cover-up.
Even if someone were to vanish,
people would only assume that she'd run away.
The diary could have been forged.
I pray that you're safe, Miss Suma.
But if you're not,
we're going to rescue you.
Another day and nothing.
Yet I can't shake this feeling something is creeping in from the fog.
How can they avoid detection with such ease?
Could it be that the demon residing here is an upper-ranked demon?
If that's the case,
we might be in for an ultra-flashy fight to the death.
It's so hot, I feel like I'm gonna die in this stupid thing!
And wearing this stupid outfit is killing my senses!
Oh, Yai, can I ask you something real quick?
Do you think Makio's adjusting here all right?
Well, she's been locked up in her room ever since she got here.
She mentioned not feeling very well,
but keeps refusing to go to a hospital.
If she doesn't do something,
the madam's going to drag her out.
I brought a meal to her room,
but she didn't come out to get it.
So I ended up having to leave it outside her door.
Makio?
That's Uzui's wife.
About time we found a new lead.
Not feeling well shouldn't be enough to stop her from checking in.
Well, if she is sick,
she'll be inside her room.
Guess I'll take a look!
Carefully, Nogo.
You'll hurt yourself rushing around like that.
What a quiet little girl.
You've got the voice of a dying animal,
so don't say a word.
Oh, and if you try putting on a girl's voice,
it'll just make you creepier.
That's even possible.
Then what am I supposed to do, damn it?
Now, then, answer me.
Who was it that you were writing all of these little letters to?
What was your name?
Oh, I remember.
It's Makio.
Isn't it?
Answer me at once, Makio.
Oh, I remember.
Thank you.
繰り返し 繰り返し 血を流す魂が 夢を見るその先に
輝いて 輝いて 新しい朝が来る 希望が 並びく
Oh yeah キミオヨンデイル エネルギー
キミオヨンデイル エネルギー
I hate that you're prettier than me.
What was that?
Now it's time for a Taisho era secret.
Zenitsu seems to have taken an interest in the Shamisen and he's actually become quite good at it.
Huh?
I'm scared to be alone in the house so can I come over to yours?
But I heard all the girls are taking an interest in you over there.
Wait, really?
Then I'm going to aspire to be the number one Oran!
Huh?
Now what?
Next episode, what are you?
Zenitsu, are you okay?
Zenitsu?
Hanandong.
Come on.
夜